Spire American Revolutionary War Collection
Spire American Revolutionary War Collection
- Miscellaneous material
  - Legal and financial papers
    - Will, Jacob Wilkins, document contesting the will of Jacob Wilkins, brought by Staats Wilkins and other heirs; mentions ownership of the Courtland (Cortlandt) Street Ferry and Steam Boat Slip in New York City (Box 2)
Clarke, Peter 1810 Jan 1 [JF], Albany, NY, to John Fisher 1810 May 22 [JF], Montezuma, NY, to John Fisher 1812 Mar 24 [JF], Albany, NY, to John Fisher 1812 Apr 29 [JF], Montezuma, NY, to John Fisher 1812 May 16 [JF], Montezuma, NY, to John Fisher 1812 Jul 7 [JF], Montezuma, NY, to John Fisher 1812 Jul 24 [JF], Marcellus, NY, to John Fisher 1813 Sep 26 [JF], Montezuma, NY, to John Fisher 1816 Dec 15 [JF], Montezuma, NY, to John Fisher
Cobb, Jabez 1802 Dec 24 [JF], Manlius, NY, to John Fisher
Cuddeback, Abraham 1780 Apr 19 [AR], to Capt. Jack DeWitt
Cuyler, Cornelius 1812 Feb 20 [JF], Scipio, NY, to John Fisher
DeLa Bretesche, Marc 1791 Aug 13 [WD], to William Duer
Delisley, John 1767 Jun 13 [GR], Montreal, to Garret Rapalje
DeLormerie 1791 Oct 24 [WD], Paris, to William Duer
Dewer(?), William 1820 Sep 6 [JF], Washington, to John Fisher
Dixon, John 1771 Oct 1 [GR], Whittington Glasshouse, to Garret Rapalje 1772 Dec 1 [GR], Shoffield, to Garret Rapalje
Duer, William 1779 Jun 11 [WD], Manor of Lívingston, to William Duer
Fisher, Helen C. 1807 Oct 1 [JF], to John Fisher 1809 [JF], Flatlands, NY, to John Fisher 1809 [JF], Narrows, NY, to John Fisher 1809 Aug 21 [JF], Narrows, NY, to John Fisher 1809 Aug 24 [JF], Narrows, NY, to John Fisher 1809 Sep 5 [JF], Narrows, NY, to John Fisher 1809 Sep 9 [JF], Narrows, NY, to John Fisher 1809 Sep 19 [JF], Narrows, NY, to John Fisher [undated] [JF], New York, to Ann Smith
Fisher, John 1798 Jun 9 [JF], New York, to Timothy Pickering 1801 Jul 16 [JF], Brooklyn, to John Harmy 1805 Apr 10 [JF], Brooklyn, to John Rapalje 1805 Apr 10 [JF], Brooklyn, to Robert Wilson 1807 Sep 24 [JF], New York, to George DePausa, Thomas Lilly, L.L. de Vaubercy circa 1812 [JF], to unidentified 1812 Apr 5 [JF], Brooklyn, to Paul I. Amerman 1812 Apr 5 [JF], Brooklyn, to Paul I. Amerman 1812 Jun 22 [JF], Brooklyn, to E.T. Throope 1812 Jul 13 [JF], Brooklyn, to Jasper Hopper 1812 Jul 13 [JF], Brooklyn, to Abraham Leggett 1812 Jul 13 [JF], Brooklyn, to Paul I. Amerman 1812 Jul 13 [JF], Brooklyn, to PauI I. Amerman 1812 Aug 13 [JF], Brooklyn, to Jasper Hopper 1813 May 7 [JF], Brooklyn, to Cornelius Cuyler 1813 Sep 18 [JF], Brooklyn, to Governor of New Jersey 1814 Aug 18 [JF], Brooklyn, to Abraham Van Vechten 1814 Jul 27 [JF], Brooklyn, to J.E. Throop 1819 Oct 23 [JF], Brooklyn, to Rev. Henry Anderdonk 1820 Jun 14 [JF], Brooklyn, to George B. Throupe 1820 Sep 20 [JF], New York, to William Dewer [Duer?] (see also Barth, Dr., 1791 Apr 15 [WD], Philadelphia, to William Duer)
Fisher, John and others 1809 Nov 2 [JF], New York, to Thomas Lilly, L.L. de Vaubercy
Ford, Samuel 1768 Nov 4 [GR], New York, to Garret Rapalje
Foreman, Joshua 1805 Sep 12 [JF], Onondaga, to John Fisher
Garsherie, Joseph 1782 Sep 13 [AR], Kingston, NY, to Gov. George Clinton
Goodrich, Selah 1806 May 24 [JF], Pompey, NY, to John Fisher
Guion, Isaac 1791 Feb 15 [WD], Gallipolis, O., to William Duer
Hay, Morey(?) 1784 May 29 [WD], to William Duer
Hiegle, Anthony J. 1765 Nov 29 [GR], Elizabeth Furnace, to Garret Rapalje
Hoffman, Joseph Ogden 1797 Dec 16 [JF], to John Fisher undated [JF], to John Fisher
Hose, John and son 1768 Jul 22 [GR], London, to Garret Rapalje
Hudson, Joseph 1796 Apr 13 [JF], Fresh Meadows, to John Fisher
Hunt and Pratt 1796 Nov 19 [JF], New York, to John Fisher
Jones, William 1787 Jun 14 [M], Charleston, to Sinickson Tuft
King, Rufus 1798 Oct 1 [M], London, to Nicholas Low
Leamen, G. 1818 May 14 [JF], Ithaca, NY, to John Fisher
LeMaistre, L. 1778 Apr 6 [AR], Quebec, to Sir John Johnson
Leonard, Nathan 1812 Mar 31 [JF], Montezuma, NY, to John Fisher 1812 Apr 3 [JF], Brutus, NY, to John Fisher 1812 Aug 25 [JF], on board steamboat, to John Fisher
Lewis, Thomas W. 1818 Sep 7 [JF], Pompey, NY, to John Fisher
L'Hanache, Alexandre 1792 Aug 6 [WD], Philadelphia, to "Milady"
Lilly, Thomas 1809 Jul 10 [JF], to Jacob Wilkins 1811 Sep 2 [JF], Baton Rouge, LA, to John Fisher 1812 Oct 7 [JF], Baton Rouge, LA, to John Fisher
Lloyd, Henry 1774 Dec 31 [GR], Boston, MA, to Garret Rapalje
Loeffler 1791 Feb 23 [WD], Philadelphia, to William Duer
Maclntosh, Phineas 1769 Oct 30 [GR], to Garret Rapalje
Marsh, WiIIiam 1779 Jul 14 [AR], Quebec, to Capt. Wilkinson
Meng, Christopher 1782 May 22 [AR], Newburgh, NY, to John Fisher
Micaull, M. 1790 Sep 10 [M], to unidentified
Mumford, Thomas 1792 Dec 4 [JF], Albany, NY, to John Fisher
Ogden, Aaron 1813 Sep 23 [JF], Elizabethtown, to John Fisher
Ogden, Nezal 1754 Jul 4 [GR], Newark, to Garret Rapalje
Peasbye, Thomas 1770 May 10 [GR], Roxbury, to Garret Rapalje
Pownall, T. 1792 Jun 11 [M], Biggleswade, Everson House, to unidentified
Ramsay, David 1790 Jul 23 [M], Charleston, to Sister 1791 Apr 31 [M], Charleston, to Sister
Rap, Walter 1817 Sep 1 [JF], Solon, to John Fisher
Rapalje, John 1800 Jun 4 [JF], Aurora, NY, to John Fisher 1803 Jan 18 [JF], Manlius, NY, to John Fisher 1805 Apr 15 [JF], Manlius, NY, to John Fisher 1805 May 9 [JF], Salina, to John Fisher 1806 Jan 9 [JF], Utica, NY, to John Fisher
Rapalje, Garret 1766 Aug [GR], New York, to Simonson & Dumont
Regineu [?] 1790 Feb 24 [WD], De Gallidolin, to William Duer
Roosa, Cornelius 1819 Oct 21 [JF], Newburgh, NY, to John Fisher
Root, Reuben 1808 April 11 [JF], Pompey, NY, to John Fisher & James B. Clarke
Simonson & Dumont 1767 Feb 10 [GR], Brookland Forge, to Garret Rapalje
Skidmore, L.L. 1824 Aug 31 [M], New York, to Mary ?
Skipwith, F. 1820 Mar 25 [JF], St. Helena Island, to John Fisher
Smith, Bernard 1774 May 23 [GR], Brooklyn, to Garret Rapalje
Smith, Samuel 1798 Aug 9 [M], Baltimore, to Ian Dayton
Spenser, Oliver 1765 Feb 6 [AR], Elizabethtown, to Joseph King
St. Bugnor(?), Lefebvre undated [WD]
St. John, Alvin, and Jabez Cobb 1803 Aug 3 [JF], Manlius, NY, to John Fisher
Stevens, John 1752 Oct 17 [M], Amboy, to Alexander
Stiles, Richard M. 1812 Aug 6 [JF], Savannah, NY, to Abram Leggett
Thacher, J. 1826 Mar 28 [JF], to unidentified
Travis, Joseph 1776 Jul 12 [AR], Peekskill, NY, to Col. Humphrey
Turton, John and Co. 1763 Mar 19 [GR], Near Birmingham, to Garret Rapalje
Tuttle, John & Joseph 1768 Mar 24 [GR], Brookland Forge, to Garret Rapalje 1768 Apr 14 [GR], Brookland Forge, to Garret Rapalje 1769 Jan 18 [GR], Brookland Forge, to Garret Rapalje 1769 Mar 7 [GR], Hanover, to Garret Rapalje 1769 Apr 3 [GR], Brookland Forge, to Garret Rapalje 1769 Apr 16 [GR], Brookland Forge, to Garret Rapalje 1769 May 16 [GR], Brookland Forge, to Garret Rapalje 1769 Jul 17 [GR], Brookland Forge, to Garret Rapalje
Tuttle, Moses 1763 Jan 4 [GR], Paquannock, N.J., to Garret Rapalje
Van Rooten, Peter 1812 Dec 10 [JF], Philadelphia, PA, to John Fisher
W.H. 1792 Jan 17 [GR], New York, to Garret Rapalje
Waldo, C. 1805 Nov 20 [JF], DaIton, to John Fisher
Wilkins, Augustus 1813 Apr 20; 1809 Dec 20 [JF], to John Fisher
Wilkins, John H. 1878 May 7 [M], Pittsburgh, to John D. Wilkins
Williams, Israel 1755 Aug 6 [M], Hatfield, MA, to Elijah Williams
Wilmot, John and others, Office of American Claims 1785 Aug 22 [AR], to Lord Sydney
Winchill, James & Amasa 1801 Jun 6 [JF], Cayuga County, to Whom it may concern
Wiswell, John 1775 May 2 [AR], to John C. Waite
Wood, Jethro 1805 Nov 3 [JF], Scipio, NY, to John Fisher
Young, John 1805 Apr 12 [JF], Manlius, NY, to John Fisher
Young, William 1768 Jul 28 [GR], Morris County, to Garret Rapalje
[unidentified] 1782 Jun 17 [WD], Philadelphia, to William Duer
[unidentified] 1790 Apr 17 [WD], Alexandria, to William Duer
[unidentified] 1792 Jan 20 [WD], Paris, to William Duer
[unidentified] undated [M], to Miss Trenchard
[unidentified] undated [WD], to unidentified